Julian Cameron

Tegvägen 26, 175 53 Järfälla | 076 429 12 57 | juliancameron 79@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A goal oriented technically minded project manager with over ten years of experience managing a variety of small and large projects within the financial and litigation sectors. Led and coordinated projects on all facets of the project's life cycle. Confident and adaptable project manager who enjoys working as part of a team and is capable of using own initiative and accepts responsibility where necessary. Fast learner that rises to any challenge.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

2005 - 2017

Production Assistant - Datasite, Merrill CorporationLondon

- Successfully Led and managed multiple Datasite and Litigation projects for blue chip financial companies and legal firms in the UK, France, Sweden Germany and Hong Kong
- Pro-actively identified and anticipated clients needs, as well as consulted and advised clients on the workflow or job production process
- Responsible for multiple client projects as point of contact, offering assistance and developing effective and positive client relationships
- · Accurately correlated, manipulated, renamed and processed client flies on Datasite
- Reliably prepared and uploaded client materials (hard and soft copy) to Datasite
- Executed and maintained accurate document and user security
- Worked with appropriate internal departments on all facets of project preparation, execution, and issue escalation
- Worked directly with the development team to test new product features and provided insightful user feedback to assist with product improvement
- Assisted in the production process, monitoring progress and ensuring that project deliverables are accurate and timely
- Ensured projects deliverables for clients are accurate and timely and monitored progress on projects deliverables
- Participated in training, mentoring and guidance of less experienced colleagues from Hong Kong, Paris, Frankfurt and St Pauls offices
- Produced daily reports and shift handovers providing direction and support to project team

- Ensured proper Salesforce documentation for job tracking via cases and notes for billing were created and maintained, and appropriately distributed
- Used Salesforce daily and regularly, achieving at least 80% call cases records

2002 - 2004

Graphic Designer / General Assistant - Connections CommunicationLondon

- · Designed promotional material for multiple EU and local authority funded media courses
- Led the in-house rebrand team for Connections Communication and sister company Ravenscourt Media
- Carried out general office duties as well as assisted IT and equipment hire sections with support for students and staff. Assisted with a number of events to showcase student's work.

EDUCATION

1999 - 2001

HND Multimedia and Graphic Design

Middlesex University, London

1995 - 1999

QNVQ Art and Design level one, two & three

St Charles Catholic Sixth Form College, London

COURSES & WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 to present

New beginners, 2B and 2C

SFI, Järfälla

SKILLS

Mac OS X, Pages, Numbers, Keynote

MS Windows: 2000, XP, 7, 10

Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, Outlook, Salesforce, Adobe Acrobat

LANGUAGES

English: native language.

Swedish: basic (speaking, reading, writing).

INTERESTS

At present, I have created a private family cloud network consisting of photos, music, artwork and legal documents with bespoke security settings. I am also an amateur photographer with an interest in nature and street photography, and in the process of producing a portfolio.

REFERENCES

Available on request.